# **Cuong Tran Le [Brandon]**

Stockton, CA 95212 (209) 244-2325 ble@codestack.co https://github.com/BrandOnLe https://www.linkedin.com/in/brandonctle

#### **SUMMARY**

Adaptable healthcare professional with a background in caregiving and pharmacy, now transitioning into software development. Skilled in handling high-stress situations and tight deadlines, gained through time-sensitive healthcare roles. Experience in developing responsive web applications utilizing a diverse range of modern technologies, including JavaScript, C#, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, and Bootstrap, as well as libraries such as React.js and Material UI.

## **SKILLS**

Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, C#, TypeScript

**Libraries & Frameworks:** React.js, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Material UI **Tools & Platforms:** Microsoft Azure, Notion, Figma, Jira, GitHub

## **EDUCATION**

# CodeStack Academy, Stockton (9/2022 - Present) Expected graduation date: 9/2023

- Completed over 1,100 hours of in-depth, project-based learning, emphasizing hands-on experience.
- Engaged in a professional learning environment that simulated real-world scenarios, including daily stand-ups and end-of-day meetings, tickets, and sprint planning.
- Acted as a project manager for a fullstack app development project, leading the development process and coordinating tasks.

#### **PROJECTS**

# Pill Pal || This project is currently in progress || Front End Repo || Back End Repo || Notion || Figma

As the project manager for Pill Pal, I took charge of designing the prototype using Figma, and outlining the entire app's features and requirements on Notion. I led a team in developing this React.js-based application, utilizing Material UI and Bootstrap components, and used Jira for task management. The goal of this app is medication adherence.

## Advice Generator | Azure | Github Repo

Developed an advice generator web application using React and Bootstrap. The project involved calling an API and recreating a product design that was provided to us. The goal was to test our ability to accurately recreate the design and incorporate API data into the application.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Health Plan of San Joaquin — Pharmacy Technician I (08/2019 - 11/2020)

- Mentored and educated new team members, sharing established processes, techniques, and best practices.
- Conducted thorough analysis of patient medical histories to assist in pharmacist decision-making during authorization requests, ensuring precise and prompt care.
- Coordinated with providers to obtain necessary approvals and clarify missing or incorrect information.
- Maintained a high level of efficiency, managing a 24-hour turnaround time processing up to 50+ requests per day during peak periods.

## CVS Pharmacy — Pharmacy Technician (08/2015 - 01/2020)

- Took on a leadership role by training new employees on pharmacy procedures and best practices, going above and beyond my assigned responsibilities.
- Implemented a daily workflow board to proactively enhance team communication and task management, streamlining workflow and increasing productivity.
- Recognizing the importance of reducing stress levels for the entire team in a high-pressure environment, I often took initiative to assist the lead technicians in their duties, allowing them to focus and not rush through important tasks.